[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"]}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "I want you to bring me up to speed with what is in this letter and how significant it may turn out to be in understanding the kind of person Ariel Castro is?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "to", "bring", "me", "up", "to", "speed", "with", "what", "is", "in", "this", "letter", "and", "how", "significant", "it", "may", "turn", "out", "to", "be", "in", "understanding", "the", "kind", "of", "person", "Ariel", "Castro", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I think when investigators get through with this letter, they're going to have a good idea of who this guy is, if he indeed wrote this letter in 2004.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "when", "investigators", "get", "through", "with", "this", "letter", ",", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "a", "good", "idea", "of", "who", "this", "guy", "is", ",", "if", "he", "indeed", "wrote", "this", "letter", "in", "2004", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "It just is extraordinary, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "just", "is", "extraordinary", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "And do you feel, Tito, that that kind of persistent rejection with women may have played a part in all this behavioral deficiency that developed inside him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "feel", ",", "Tito", ",", "that", "that", "kind", "of", "persistent", "rejection", "with", "women", "may", "have", "played", "a", "part", "in", "all", "this", "behavioral", "deficiency", "that", "developed", "inside", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "At first I never thought anything of it until I started hearing all the news, stuff about him, and thinking about it now, I'm like it could be, maybe he resented these women who they didn't want to dance with him for whatever the reasons were.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "first", "I", "never", "thought", "anything", "of", "it", "until", "I", "started", "hearing", "all", "the", "news", ",", "stuff", "about", "him", ",", "and", "thinking", "about", "it", "now", ",", "I", "'m", "like", "it", "could", "be", ",", "maybe", "he", "resented", "these", "women", "who", "they", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "dance", "with", "him", "for", "whatever", "the", "reasons", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tito"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "When you think about it now with hindsight, it makes more sense?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "think", "about", "it", "now", "with", "hindsight", ",", "it", "makes", "more", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "When I went to his house two years ago, like I say, I sold him some appliances.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "went", "to", "his", "house", "two", "years", "ago", ",", "like", "I", "say", ",", "I", "sold", "him", "some", "appliances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Can anyone quite believe that Ariel Castro, this apparently nice, normal guy, has turned out to be allegedly this horrific monster?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "anyone", "quite", "believe", "that", "Ariel", "Castro", ",", "this", "apparently", "nice", ",", "normal", "guy", ",", "has", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "allegedly", "this", "horrific", "monster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "No, everybody's been shocked, shocked to the point where they really don't want to talk about it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "everybody", "'s", "been", "shocked", ",", "shocked", "to", "the", "point", "where", "they", "really", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Very good, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Is there a sense of, yes, great joy these women have been found, but also a sense of collective guilt that the community and the police and everyone working together were unable to find any of them in ten years?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "sense", "of", ",", "yes", ",", "great", "joy", "these", "women", "have", "been", "found", ",", "but", "also", "a", "sense", "of", "collective", "guilt", "that", "the", "community", "and", "the", "police", "and", "everyone", "working", "together", "were", "unable", "to", "find", "any", "of", "them", "in", "ten", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "That's definitely true, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "definitely", "true", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "You believe that he was a bit of a manipulator, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "believe", "that", "he", "was", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "manipulator", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Why did you fire him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "fire", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, with stuff like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "with", "stuff", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March 13"]}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "NNP", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "When did you last hear from him?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "last", "hear", "from", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I actually heard -- March 13, I got some texts from him, of this year, that he really wanted to come back with the band.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "heard", "--", "March", "13", ",", "I", "got", "some", "texts", "from", "him", ",", "of", "this", "year", ",", "that", "he", "really", "wanted", "to", "come", "back", "with", "the", "band", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Looking back on the time you spent with him, particularly at the house, was there anything that happened in all that time that when you look at it now, you think, OK, now I get what may have been going on?", "question_tokens": ["Looking", "back", "on", "the", "time", "you", "spent", "with", "him", ",", "particularly", "at", "the", "house", ",", "was", "there", "anything", "that", "happened", "in", "all", "that", "time", "that", "when", "you", "look", "at", "it", "now", ",", "you", "think", ",", "OK", ",", "now", "I", "get", "what", "may", "have", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "EX", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Honestly, Mr. Morgan, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "Mr.", "Morgan", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Did you see any of that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "No, I only saw the very social, happy go lucky guy on the block.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "only", "saw", "the", "very", "social", ",", "happy", "go", "lucky", "guy", "on", "the", "block", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Other than shock, what are you all thinking?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "shock", ",", "what", "are", "you", "all", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "He was -- we don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "--", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Do you feel guilty, Juan, that you were so close to these girls and you weren't able to help them, even though you knew nothing about what was happening?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "guilty", ",", "Juan", ",", "that", "you", "were", "so", "close", "to", "these", "girls", "and", "you", "were", "n't", "able", "to", "help", "them", ",", "even", "though", "you", "knew", "nothing", "about", "what", "was", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Juan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Do you think now he was using -- not yours, but some of the others, right?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "now", "he", "was", "using", "--", "not", "yours", ",", "but", "some", "of", "the", "others", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "RB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "But do you think his intention, Storm, in doing this was to hide out any possible noises from his -- the women that he captured?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "his", "intention", ",", "Storm", ",", "in", "doing", "this", "was", "to", "hide", "out", "any", "possible", "noises", "from", "his", "--", "the", "women", "that", "he", "captured", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "He had dogs in that yard.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "dogs", "in", "that", "yard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Where does this man, Ariel Castro, assuming he gets convicted of all the crimes we believe he's done -- where does he rank in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "this", "man", ",", "Ariel", "Castro", ",", "assuming", "he", "gets", "convicted", "of", "all", "the", "crimes", "we", "believe", "he", "'s", "done", "--", "where", "does", "he", "rank", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "He's up there.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "John, the big question, I guess, is could there be other serious crimes that Ariel Castro has committed, given that this period only starts, really, in his 40s?", "question_tokens": ["John", ",", "the", "big", "question", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "is", "could", "there", "be", "other", "serious", "crimes", "that", "Ariel", "Castro", "has", "committed", ",", "given", "that", "this", "period", "only", "starts", ",", "really", ",", "in", "his", "40s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "When you get an offender at this age, in his 40s like this, usually, it begins -- OK, let's give you a this is your life kind of thing with violent offenders.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "you", "get", "an", "offender", "at", "this", "age", ",", "in", "his", "40s", "like", "this", ",", "usually", ",", "it", "begins", "--", "OK", ",", "let", "'s", "give", "you", "a", "this", "is", "your", "life", "kind", "of", "thing", "with", "violent", "offenders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Do you think, John, that if Amanda Berry hasn't shown the courage she did to escape at the start of this week, that her own daughter that she had with this man could have come into his target- range, in terms of being a sexual tool for him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", ",", "John", ",", "that", "if", "Amanda", "Berry", "has", "n't", "shown", "the", "courage", "she", "did", "to", "escape", "at", "the", "start", "of", "this", "week", ",", "that", "her", "own", "daughter", "that", "she", "had", "with", "this", "man", "could", "have", "come", "into", "his", "target-", "range", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "being", "a", "sexual", "tool", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Very definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John", "Amanda Berry"]}}]